This is the second time I've seen a
little-faceted vehicle.
This one is a present one, but it's a
vehicle of four people.
And this one is the same.
One, five of our people, and a third of
course.
And that's a cross.
We're about to discover a city that's rich
beyond measure.
Those in power are obsessed with records.
Everything has to be bigger, better, and
more expensive than anywhere else.
Our guide shows us what he describes as a
gigantic luxurious paradise.
Huge buildings go by, all marble and
grandiose architecture.
The roofs of the buildings are all green
or red, the colours of the flag.
Another rule imposed by the authorities.
I've seen everything white.
And if a collod car comes in the capital,
what happens?
You can use a taxi.
You can invite the friends, take a rent
car.
This is the capital of our country,
and we want to show as more beautiful as
possible.
This strange structure is another record.
This is the world's largest indoor wheel,
47 meters high.
We are alone in the whole caravan, there
is only us.
But as far as we can see, there is no one
in the park.
There is not a single human being.
There is absolutely no one.
That's the feeling we've had since our
arrival.
Although the country officially has 7
million inhabitants, we didn't see many of
them in the capital.
From above, we could see huge gardens, but
not a living soul for miles around.
There was a weird feeling of being in a
ghost town.